<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MIT Renewable Energy Clinic</title>
	<atom:link href="https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 15:56:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/Logo.svg</url>
	<title>MIT Renewable Energy Clinic</title>
	<link>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Larry Susskind</title>
		<link>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/emma-jung/</link>
					<comments>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/emma-jung/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[PI]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/?p=585</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Principal Investigator is Larry Susskind, Ford Professor of Urban and Environmental Planning in the MIT Department of Urban Studies and Planning and Vice-Chair of the inter-university Program on Negotiation at Harvard Law School. Professor Susskind is well known in the urban and environmental planning fields for his published work on facility siting, collaborative approaches [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Principal Investigator is Larry Susskind, Ford Professor of Urban and Environmental Planning in the MIT Department of Urban Studies and Planning and Vice-Chair of the inter-university Program on Negotiation at Harvard Law School. Professor Susskind is well known in the urban and environmental planning fields for his published work on facility siting, collaborative approaches to public policymaking, and decarbonization. He has supervised more than 75 doctoral dissertations and 150 master’s theses at MIT. He is an applied social scientist with background in public policy, public administration, environmental planning, negotiation and dispute resolution, social entrepreneurship, and conflict resolution.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/emma-jung/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jungwoo Chun</title>
		<link>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/grace-pu/</link>
					<comments>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/grace-pu/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Grad Student]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/?p=584</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Jungwoo Chun is a postdoctoral impact fellow at the MIT Climate and Sustainability Consortium (MCSC) and a lecturer at the Department of Urban Studies and Planning (DUSP) at MIT. His dissertation involved investigating clusters of intermediaries that support community ownership of solar energy projects in the United States. He has extensive research, teaching, and professional [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="c-message_kit__gutter">
<div class="c-message_kit__gutter__right" role="presentation" data-qa="message_content">
<div class="c-message_kit__blocks c-message_kit__blocks--rich_text">
<div class="c-message__message_blocks c-message__message_blocks--rich_text" data-qa="message-text">
<div class="p-block_kit_renderer" data-qa="block-kit-renderer">
<div class="p-block_kit_renderer__block_wrapper p-block_kit_renderer__block_wrapper--first">
<div class="p-rich_text_block" dir="auto">
<div class="p-rich_text_section">Jungwoo Chun is a postdoctoral impact fellow at the MIT Climate and Sustainability Consortium (MCSC) and a lecturer at the Department of Urban Studies and Planning (DUSP) at MIT. His dissertation involved investigating clusters of intermediaries that support community ownership of solar energy projects in the United States. He has extensive research, teaching, and professional experience related to various aspects of climate change and sustainability with a particular focus on public dispute mediation. He currently teaches 11.255 Negotiation and Dispute Resolution in the Public Sector and holds a Ph.D. in Environmental Policy and Planning from MIT DUSP.</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/grace-pu/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Anushree Chaudhuri</title>
		<link>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/anushree-chaudhuri/</link>
					<comments>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/anushree-chaudhuri/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:09:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[UROP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/?p=586</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Anushree is an undergraduate student at MIT studying urban planning and economics. She&#8217;s interested in bringing a data-focused perspective to environmental policy and social impact. She joined the Science Impact Collaborative in 2021. As a native San Diegan with origins in Bengal, India, she grew up eager to bridge gaps between people of diverse identities. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Anushree is an undergraduate student at MIT studying urban planning and economics. She&#8217;s interested in bringing a data-focused perspective to environmental policy and social impact. She joined the Science Impact Collaborative in 2021. As a native San Diegan with origins in Bengal, India, she grew up eager to bridge gaps between people of diverse identities. She&#8217;s co-chair of the Undergraduate Association Committee on Sustainability, a lead of the Student Sustainability Coalition, and plays on the Women&#8217;s Ultimate Frisbee team. In her free time, she loves reading and writing, plant-based cooking, yoga, world music, going on long walks with her dog, and learning new things.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/anushree-chaudhuri/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>David Beron</title>
		<link>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/david-beron/</link>
					<comments>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/david-beron/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/?p=1186</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[David is a Master in City Planning candidate at MIT’s Department of Urban Studies and Planning. He has a background in economics and environmental studies and worked on public service delivery projects in Colombia prior to joining the Renewable Energy Facility Siting Clinic in the fall of 2022.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>David is a Master in City Planning candidate at MIT’s Department of Urban Studies and Planning. He has a background in economics and environmental studies and worked on public service delivery projects in Colombia prior to joining the Renewable Energy Facility Siting Clinic in the fall of 2022.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/david-beron/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sanjana Paul</title>
		<link>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/sanjana-paul/</link>
					<comments>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/sanjana-paul/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 00:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Grad Student]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/?p=1145</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Sanjana Paul is a technical associate focusing on the City Scanner project at MIT&#8217;s Senseable City Lab. She holds a bachelor&#8217;s degree in electrical engineering and physics, and is the executive director and co-founder of Earth Hacks, an environmental hackathon organization. Previously, she worked as an atmospheric science software developer at NASA, an NSF REU [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="col-md-9 pece-layouts-content panel-panel">
<div class="panel-panel-inner">
<div class="panel-pane pane-entity-field pane-profile2-field-pece-biography">
<div class="pane-content">
<div class="field field-name-field-pece-biography field-type-text-long field-label-hidden">
<div class="field-items">
<div class="field-item even">
<p>Sanjana Paul is a technical associate focusing on the City Scanner project at MIT&#8217;s Senseable City Lab. She holds a bachelor&#8217;s degree in electrical engineering and physics, and is the executive director and co-founder of Earth Hacks, an environmental hackathon organization. Previously, she worked as an atmospheric science software developer at NASA, an NSF REU participant in extreme ultraviolet engineering in the Kapteyn-Murnane Lab in JILA at the University of Colorado Boulder, and as a Conservation Innovation Fellow at Conservation X Labs.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/sanjana-paul/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jess Cohen</title>
		<link>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/katherine-xiong/</link>
					<comments>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/katherine-xiong/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[UROP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/?p=582</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Jess is an undergraduate at MIT, majoring in Physics with a focus in Materials Science and Engineering and minoring in Energy Studies. They are from New York State and have a younger sister. They went to Spackenkill High School where they worked with Dr. Hailiang Wang at Yale University for 3 years on bifunctional catalysis [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jess is an undergraduate at MIT, majoring in Physics with a focus in Materials Science and Engineering and minoring in Energy Studies. They are from New York State and have a younger sister. They went to Spackenkill High School where they worked with Dr. Hailiang Wang at Yale University for 3 years on bifunctional catalysis for carbon dioxide reduction. In the past at MIT, they have performed research in the Manthiram lab for two years on electrochemical xylene reduction and with Dr. Tracy Slatyer on Fermi Bubble radiation. They have interned at the Strasbourg City Government as well as with a start up at Greentown Labs. They are currently involved with MIT Divest as well as the College Climate Coalition and are greatly interested in environmental justice issues, especially surrounding energy. In their free time they enjoy reading, playing violin, and skiing.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/katherine-xiong/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Grace Endy</title>
		<link>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/kenneth-choi/</link>
					<comments>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/kenneth-choi/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[UROP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/?p=575</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Grace Endy is a first-year undergraduate student from Westfield, New Jersey. She attended Westfield High School, where she was president of the Rare Disease Club and a member of the varsity cross country and track and field teams. While in high school, Grace volunteered for KIF1A.ORG, creating videos that helped make information about KIF1A-Associated Neurological [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Grace Endy is a first-year undergraduate student from Westfield, New Jersey. She attended Westfield High School, where she was president of the Rare Disease Club and a member of the varsity cross country and track and field teams. While in high school, Grace volunteered for KIF1A.ORG, creating videos that helped make information about KIF1A-Associated Neurological Disorder more accessible for affected families. She is very passionate about combating climate change and is thus interested in studying renewable energy and energy policy. She plans on majoring in chemical engineering. Outside of class, Grace is currently involved with the MIT Running Club and also enjoys baking, reading, hiking, and spending time with her family.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/kenneth-choi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kano Tungkitkancharoen</title>
		<link>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/kevin-meng/</link>
					<comments>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/kevin-meng/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[UROP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/?p=574</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Kano is an undergraduate at MIT from Las Vegas, Nevada. She’s studying mechanical engineering and political science. The highlight job of her gap year was serving as the youngest person on the 2020 Nevada Biden Presidential Data Team. At the MIT 2021 Policy Hackathon, Kano&#8217;s team advanced to finals, reaching Top 3. Outside of political [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Kano is an undergraduate at MIT from Las Vegas, Nevada. She’s studying mechanical engineering and political science. The highlight job of her gap year was serving as the youngest person on the 2020 Nevada Biden Presidential Data Team. At the MIT 2021 Policy Hackathon, Kano&#8217;s team advanced to finals, reaching Top 3. Outside of political activities, Kano loves to build things. In high school, she served as President of VEX Robotics, where she qualified and attended the Robotics World Championship. She was also the Build Captain of Science Olympiad, where she’s qualified and attended the Science Olympiad National Tournament. She’s also conducted independent research on the engineering design of addiction in slot machines through analysis of MRI imaging under the guidance of Professor Daniel Sahl at the UNLV Gaming Innovation Lab. Kano is fascinated by both engineering and political systems because they’re both all about making different things work together in a system towards a common goal. She hopes to apply her interest in building machines and crafting thoughtful policies to advance clean energy. In her free time, Kano enjoys meditating, crafting music playlists, and hunting for spice challenges.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>hare a passion for STEM and look to transform their ideas into reality!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/kevin-meng/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sarah Pomerantz</title>
		<link>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/sarah-pomerantz/</link>
					<comments>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/sarah-pomerantz/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[UROP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/?p=572</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Sarah is an undergraduate student from Long Island, New York. She attended Half Hollow Hills High School West, where was president of the Gay Straight Alliance and vice president of FIRST Tech Challenge Robotics Club and their chapter of Mu Alpha Theta. Outside of this project, Sarah is a MedLink in her dorm, Simmons Hall, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Sarah is an undergraduate student from Long Island, New York. She attended Half Hollow Hills High School West, where was president of the Gay Straight Alliance and vice president of FIRST Tech Challenge Robotics Club and their chapter of Mu Alpha Theta. Outside of this project, Sarah is a MedLink in her dorm, Simmons Hall, and is a Freshman Recruitment of Simmons Hall (FROSH) Chair, where she plans Campus Preview Weekend and Residence Exploration Week activities. Sarah is also on the MIT Solar Electric Vehicle Team where she works on the electrical engineering subteam. During her free time, Sarah enjoys spending time with her friends!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/sarah-pomerantz/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Alice Zehner</title>
		<link>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/alice-zehner/</link>
					<comments>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/alice-zehner/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[UROP]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/?p=981</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Alice contributed to this project in the fall of 2021.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Alice contributed to this project in the fall of 2021.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://renewable-energy.mit.edu/alice-zehner/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
